

Contact information

Tulsa, USA • abikilborn@gmail.com

Professional summary

User-focused Front End Developer with 3 years of professional experience and 5 years of total experience. Built multiple SaaS applications from the ground up using modern front-end frameworks and tools. Experienced in start-up teams and fast-paced environments. Committed to quality, teamwork, detail, and growth. Specializing in Vue, TailwindCSS, Javascript, and pixel-perfect design implementation.

Employment history

Front End Developer

Backlt — Aug, 2022 - Present

- Developed responsive web pages using Vue, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to enhance the user experience and improve the overall performance of the website.
- Stayed up-to-date with the latest trends and best practices in front-end development and UX/UI design to provide innovative solutions and drive continuous improvement in website performance and user experience.
- Conducted regular competitor analysis to identify opportunities and make recommendations for improving the website's overall look and user experience
- Designed, implemented, and deployed MVP within 4 months

Front End Developer

Veedback — Sep, 2020 - Aug, 2022

- Collaborated with the marketing team to create visually appealing and user-friendly website designs that align with the company's branding and messaging strategies.
- Began and continued in a UX/UI Design role alongside this Front End Development role
- Created wireframes and prototypes to test and validate user interfaces
- Gathered and analyzed feedback from users to identify pain points and areas for improvement in the website design and user experience.
- Successfully implemented an app redesign with a turnaround time of 7 days, resulting in an increase in customer response rate for brands.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Western Oregon University, Monmouth, OR — Sep, 2018 - Jun, 2020

Associates of Arts Degree

Chemeketa Community College, Salem, OR — Sep, 2016 - Jun, 2018

Nuxt HTML CSS Figma Agile Methodologies JavaScript Git RESTful APIs UX/UI Design

Links

Skills

<u>Portfolio</u>

<u>LinkedIn</u>